Previously on Reacher...
《烈探雷徹》前情提要
I got your message.
我收到你的消息了
110th, 10-30. A distress call.
110特別調查組 “10-30” 這是求救信號
Calvin Franz was murdered.
卡爾文弗朗茨被謀殺了
If he was calling you for help, he may have been trying to get in touch with the rest of the unit.
如果他給你打過電話 那他可能也給隊里其他人打過
I called O'Donnell, Dixon, Sanchez and Orozco. No one's answering.
我給奧唐納 迪克森 桑切斯 和奧羅斯科打了電話 都沒人接
I paid off the concierge.
我買通了門房
He I.D.'d Neagley as checking in.
他指認內格利登記入住
Just keep an eye on that hotel and them.
盯緊那家酒店還有他們
No one will really know who you are. But you know.
- 沒人會知道你是誰 - 但你知道
Hey, O'Donnell. Hey, Neagley.
- 嘿 奧唐納 - 嘿 內格利
Just a list of names, all starting with the initials "A.M."
只是一個名單 所有名字的首字母都是AM
I just got page after page of random numbers.
我剛得到的是一頁又一頁的隨機數據
No order, no meaning. Nothing. At least to us, for now.
- 沒有順序 沒有意義 什么都沒 - 至少我們覺得沒有 而且暫時而已
What are you thinking?
你有什么想法
I'm thinking there's someone hell-bent on taking out the special investigators.
我覺得有人一心想干掉特別調查員
And they're coming after us.
他們是沖我們來的
Good.
很好
So, if someone's coming after the 110, how come they haven't made a run at the three of us yet?
如果他們的目標是110小組 那他們怎么還沒殺我們
You were in the woods with your family, no one can ever find me
你之前跟家人在樹林里 沒人能找到我
and maybe they just hadn't gotten around to Neagley yet.
或許還沒輪到內格利
They were in our hotel rooms,
他們去了我們的酒店房間
maybe to grab us or take us out, but then had to bail for some reason.
也許他們是想抓或者殺了我們 隨后因故不得不匆忙離開
We need to try again to warn the others.
我們得再試著警告其他人
I'll call Sanchez and Orozco. I got Dixon.
- 我會給桑切斯和奧羅斯科打電話 - 我來聯系迪克森
There's a black sedan across the street, couple houses down.
街對面幾棟房子外有一輛黑色轎車
Same one as yesterday.
跟昨天遇到的是同一輛
Guess you were right. We're being followed.
我猜你說得對 我們被跟蹤了
How you want to play this?
你打算怎么處理
I'm gonna go introduce myself.
我要去做個自我介紹
Look at this fucking beaut.
看看這個該死的美男子
What's he think he's gonna do?
他打算干什么呢
Fucking nose, man.
我他媽的鼻子 兄弟
Gun!
有槍
Just like the good old days.
就像過去美好的時光
Yeah, you on the sidelines while I do all the work.
是啊 你在一旁觀望 而我把所有工作都做完了
Uh, fellas, this was his gun.
伙計們 這是他的槍
NYPD?
紐約市警察局
Name's Gaitano Russo.
名叫蓋塔諾拉索
Don't look at me. You did all the work.
嘿 別看我 你把所有工作都做完了
Got to say, man. Major screwup.
我得說 兄弟 你闖大禍了
Soon as Russo wakes up, the entire NYPD's gonna be after your ass.
拉索一醒來 整個紐約市警察局都會追捕你
Why'd you got to hit him so hard, huh?
你為什么下手那么狠
I don't hit soft.
我出手從不手軟
Well, a cop puncher's gonna do some serious time. I was pissed about the dog,
- 襲警可是要坐很久的牢 - 那只狗的事情讓我很生氣
and I assumed he was involved in killing Franzy and Swan.
我以為他參與了殺害弗朗茨和斯旺
What did you teach us? "In an investigation, assumptions kill."
你怎么教我們的  “在調查中 假設害死人”
No, it was "In an investigation, details matter".
是“在調查時 細節至關重要”
I didn't kill him, just broke his nose. He'll be fine when he wakes up.
我沒殺他 只是打斷了他的鼻子 他醒來時會沒事的
Shit. Gaitano Russo.
糟了 蓋塔諾拉索
Guy Russo. He's the investigating officer in Franz's homicide.
又叫蓋伊拉索 他是弗朗茨謀殺案的調查人員
I saw it in the files. And how'd he get on your tail?
- 我在檔案中看到過他的名字 - 他是怎么開始跟蹤你的
NYPD saw the calls Franz made to you, flagged your name,
紐約市警察局看到弗朗茨 給你打了電話 標記了你的名字
got an alert when you bought the plane tickets,
你買票的時候 他們收到了提醒
been on you since you landed. Question is "why?"
自從你落地以后一直跟著你 問題是 為什么
Question is "where?"
問題是 哪里
As in, where do we hide a six-foot-five felon so you don't wind up in the pokey.
哪里可以藏一個近兩米的重罪犯 這樣你就不會被關進監獄了
I'm not leaving. The case is here.
我不走 這里是案發現場
Maybe not.
也許不是
When I called Sanchez and Orozco's office, voice mail was full.
我給桑切斯和奧羅斯科的辦公室 打電話時 語音信箱已經滿了
That's a bad sign.
這是個噩兆
So it might not be a bad time to get out of Dodge,
考慮到這位“拳王” 擊倒了一位執法人員
considering Cocky Balboa here just knocked out a lawman.
現在出去避風頭或許不失為好主意
Fine. We'll head down to Atlantic City,
好吧 我們去大西洋城
see if we can find the guys.
看我們能不能找到那些人
First we got to check out of our hotel and find a more generic ride
首先 我們要退房 并在拉索恢復知覺
before Russo regains consciousness and puts out a BOLO.
讓警方“小心提防”你之前 找到更普通的交通工具
Range Rover's too conspicuous.
路虎攬勝太顯眼了
You're the reason we can't have nice things.
就是因為你 我們才不能用好東西
Wait, I don't understand. Was it a car accident?
等等 我不明白 是出車禍了嗎
No, he just kicked the car.
沒有 他就踹了一下車
Well, then how the hell did the airbag go off?
好吧 那為什么 安全氣囊都彈出來了
He kicked the car,
他踹了一下車
then he pulled the cop out and he knocked his dick in the dirt.
然后把警察拉了出來 狠狠地揍了一頓
I'm telling you, this guy's a beast.
這家伙就是頭野獸
When the time comes, I'm gonna need some backup.
到時候 我需要支援
And you'll get it.
會給你安排支援的
But for now, you just stay on their asses, and don't fuck this up.
但現在 你繼續跟蹤監視他們 別搞砸了
Understood.
明白
Short-term airport parking only in Lot 1.
機場臨時停車僅在一號停車場
There's a 2019 Accord for sale up in Tremont for way under market value.
特里蒙特有輛2019款雅閣 正在出售 價格低于市場價
Cash-only deal.
僅限現金交易
One of the most stolen makes and models for sale in the Bronx, and the guy wants no paperwork?
布朗克斯區最常被盜的車型之一 他不想要任何文件嗎
We sit in that thing, we burn our asses.
我們坐進去 就跟火燒屁股一樣
We don't have a choice. We're flagged in the system. We can't rent anything under our names.
我們別無選擇 我們被警方標記了 什么都租不了
Well, we drive around in a stolen vehicle, we risk getting pinched.
我們開著偷來的車到處走 那很有可能被逮捕
I've got our solution.
我有解決辦法了
How was your undercover job?
你的臥底工作怎么樣了
Reacher.
雷徹
How'd you know I was undercover?
你怎么知道我在臥底
Considering the circumstances, you would've come right away.
考慮到當時的情況 你會馬上過來
But you didn't, which can only mean you didn't get our messages until recently.
但你沒有 這意味著 你最近才收到我們的消息
But if you were on vacation, you would've checked in with your office periodically.
如果你在休假 你會向你的辦公室匯報
So you had to be working undercover, deep undercover,
所以你一定是去做臥底了 還藏得很深
where frequent check-ins aren't always possible.
沒辦法頻繁簽到
Same old Reacher.
你還是一如既往地厲害啊
Corporate embezzlement case.
我在調查一起企業貪污案
Stuck in Texas so long, I started to think
在德克薩斯州待了很久
I actually liked cowboy boots and high school football.
久到我都開始覺得自己 喜歡牛仔靴和高中橄欖球了
Still got your fake ID with you?
你還帶著假身份證嗎
- Yeah. - Good.
- 帶著呢 - 很好
Use it to rent the car. What's with all the secrecy?
- 拿它去租車吧 - 為什么要保密
Neagley, O'Donnell and I have been flagged in the system.
內格利 奧唐納和我被警方標記了
And I punched out a cop.
我還打暈了一名警察
Of course you did.
好吧 并不意外
So...
那么
Franz.
弗朗茨...
Yeah.
是的
And Swan, most likely.
斯旺也兇多吉少
Sanchez and Orozco are MIA, too.
桑切斯和奧羅斯科也失蹤了
Okay.
好吧
Okay, so we take care of business.
好吧 那我們來調查吧
You do not mess with the special investigators.
不要惹特別調查員
Next.
接下來
Make sure you get an... SUV. I know. You need the headroom.
- 一定要租一輛... - SUV 我知道 你需要車內空間高點
Good. Glad to see you're still here.
太好了 很高興看到你還在這里
Feel like I'm never gonna leave.
感覺我永遠都不會離開
If it's reported at any Army base anywhere in the world,
如果世界上任何一個 軍事基地報告了任何違規行為
no matter how minor the infraction, we're copied on it.
無論多么輕微 我們都得處理
Well, anything jump out at you?
你發現什么特別的事了嗎
Yeah, a rat the size of a honeydew about 20 minutes ago.
是的 20分鐘前 有一只蜜露大小的老鼠
- Seriously? - Yeah.
說真的
It's back in those boxes somewhere.
它又回到那堆箱子那邊了
Gross.
好惡心
Well, speaking of rats, I think I smell one.
說到老鼠 我覺得 我發現了一只可疑的“老鼠”
A commanding officer at a base in Afghanistan thinks someone's stealing aviation fuel.
阿富汗的一名指揮官 認為有人在偷航空燃料
Siphoning off gas to resell it on the side?
把汽油抽走 然后再賣出去
Not exactly the kind of priority case the Army wants us taking on.
這不是軍方想讓我們優先處理的案子
Right, but see, I don't think anybody's stealing and reselling anything.
我覺得并不是有人在偷取并倒賣燃料
Take a look at these numbers. They always tell a story.
看看這些數字 它們總能說明問題
See, I noticed that every time fuel went missing from the base,
我注意到每次基地里有燃料丟失時
it was always after a specific flight.
都是在一趟特定的航班之后
Whenever C-17s ferried Humvees back home to the States.
即每當C-17 將悍馬車運回美國的時候
I mean, it's a minor detail, but in an investigation, details matter.
我的意思是 這是個小細節 但在調查時 細節至關重要
I like that.
我喜歡這句
I'm gonna use it.
我會說這句的
What's mine is yours.
我的就是你的
So...
那么
you have a theory?
你推測出來了嗎
Yeah. There's been no indication of black market fuel sales
是的 沒有跡象表明基地附近
anywhere on or around the base,
存在黑市燃料銷售的情況
so how does all that fuel go missing?
那這些燃料是怎么消失的呢
Best way to make gas disappear is to burn it up.
讓燃料消失的最佳方式 就是把它燒了
Exactly. Now, Neagley's got the bulk fuel experience
沒錯 內格利有儲藏運輸石油的經驗
and she thinks all the Humvee flights are intentionally being over-fueled.
她認為所有運送悍馬的航班 都是故意過度加油的
But, when those planes land,
但當這些飛機降落時
the amount of fuel in the tanks is exactly what's expected,
油箱中的燃油量與預期相符
and that gets logged into the books.
這些都被記錄到賬簿中了
So, how does that happen?
怎么會這樣
The excess fuel is being used to transport more weight
多余的燃料是在飛機運輸不為人知的
than people realize is on the plane. Yeah.
- 額外貨物的過程中消耗掉的 - 對
Something heavy and secret is being moved.
運輸了一些沉重而秘密的東西
Exactly. Contraband in the Humvees.
沒錯 悍馬車里有違禁品
Drugs, guns, stolen cash, all of the above.
毒品 槍支 被盜現金 上述所有
Good work, Dixon.
干得好 迪克森
You just found a case worthy of our attention.
你找到了一起值得我們關注的案子
I don't know about you, but all this sleuthing's made me thirsty.
我不知道你的感覺 但這些調查讓我口干舌燥
Want to go celebrate?
想去慶祝一下嗎
You can buy me a drink.
你可以請我喝一杯
I got to keep working on these reports.
我得繼續處理這些報告
Maybe next time. Yeah.
- 下次吧 - 好的
But again,
但再說一次
excellent work, Dixon. Yeah.
- 干得好 迪克森 - 是啊
No problem. Like I said, numbers always tell the story.
沒問題 如我所說 數字總能說明問題
So, the numbers telling you a story?
這些數字跟你說明問題了嗎
Yeah, and it's a David Lynch film. It's totally incomprehensible.
是的 但這就像晦澀難懂的電影 完全無法理解
I mean, if these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
如果這些是分數 那寫下這些數字的人就太粗心了
Some of them aren't even reduced.
有些沒被約分
I noticed that, too.
我也注意到了這一點
Maybe the numbers represent hard quantities.
也許這些數據代表數量
Like, eight out of ten somethings, and not just four-fifths of something?
比如 十分之八的某物 而不是五分之四的某物
Maybe.
有可能
Yeah, maybe. Beyond that, two things stick out.
嗯 有可能 除此以外 還有兩件事很突出
None of these are 100%, meaning there's no nine out of nine
這里面沒有百分之百 也就是說沒有九分之九
or ten out of ten, and the first four pages have 26 numbers,
或十分之十 前四頁有26個數字
the fifth has 27 and the last two have 26 again.
第五頁有27個 最后兩頁又是26個
Could be an accident. Just the way the information's spaced.
可能是巧合 只是信息的羅列方式
No, seems deliberate to me. None of these pages are full.
看起來是刻意而為之的 每一頁都不滿
What about the list of A.M. names?
那一連串AM開頭的名字呢
Means nothing to me. I agree with you guys. It's got to be an alias.
沒有任何意義 我同意你們的看法 應該是化名
Maybe it's someone with a grudge against the 110th?
也許是對110小組懷恨在心的人
We've arrested a lot of people.
我們逮捕了很多人
What about James Barr?
詹姆斯巴爾呢
I mean, that guy's got the skills and a screw loose.
他技術高明 有神經質
Barr's a shooter. Can't picture him throwing someone out of a helicopter.
巴爾是名射手 無法想象 他把人從直升機上扔下去的畫面
Plus, I ran into him in Indiana last year.
我去年在印第安納州遇見了他
He owes me now.
他現在欠我人情
I don't want to know.
我不想知道
Pine Barrens.
“松林荒原”
About a million lonely acres.
大約有一百萬英畝
A lot like the spot Upstate New York where they found Franz.
很像他們在紐約北部 發現弗朗茨尸體的地方
They left his broken body out there to rot.
他們把他破碎的尸體扔在那里 任其腐爛
For all we know, Swan's out there, too.
據我們所知 斯旺也在那里
And Sanchez. And Orozco.
還有桑切斯和奧羅斯科
There's no blues station?
沒有布魯斯電臺嗎
Bro, we're in Jersey.
兄弟 我們現在在澤西
It's from my phone.
是我手機上的
Franz used to blast this at HQ all the time when you weren't around.
以前你不在的時候 弗朗茨總是在總部大聲放這首歌
Leave it.
放著吧
They rented a car under a fake name, but it's, uh, it's Karla Dixon.
他們用假名字租了一輛車 但是是卡拉迪克森去租的
She's with them now.
她現在跟他們匯合了
They're headed towards Atlantic City, probably gonna try to find their missing buddies.
他們前往大西洋城 可能是去找他們的伙伴
Good. All in the same place at once.
很好 一個地方 一網打盡
When you get there, take them out.
你到大西洋城以后 殺了他們
Copy that.
收到
You remember what I said about needing backup? I know some local talent.
你還記得我說過我需要支援嗎  我認識一些當地的人才
Well, bring in whoever you need.
你需要誰 盡管帶上
We'll cover the tab.
我們會付錢
I just want them dead by tomorrow.
我只希望你明天干掉他們
You hear me? Fucking dead.
聽見了嗎 讓他們死翹翹
Just like Franz's office.
就像弗朗茨的辦公室一樣
And our hotel rooms.
還像我們的酒店房間
You said they hadn't trashed Swan's place.
你說過他們洗劫了斯旺的住處
Yup. Add that to the list of things
- 是的 - 把那加入事物列表
that must mean something.
一定意味著什么
You guys ever know Orozco to go anywhere without his lighter?
你們知道奧羅斯科 會不帶打火機出門嗎
Better days.
美好時光
Am I the only one of us that doesn't have this photo?
只有我一個人沒有這張照片嗎
- Got mine. - Got mine.
- 我有 - 我有
On my bookshelf.
我的放在書架上
Hard to hang a picture on your wall when you don't have walls.
家里沒有墻的話 很難把它掛墻上
We're wasting our time here.
我們在這里是浪費時間
Agreed. We have what the killers want, and anything worth finding,
我同意 我們有兇手想要的東西 所有值得找的東西
they already got.
他們已經得手了
Where to next?
接下來去哪兒
A bar.
去一家酒吧
Look at these photos of Sanchez and this woman.
看看桑切斯和這個女人的這些照片
Who under 50 frames photos? We do.
- 五十歲以下的人誰還會裱照片啊  - 我們會
Other than the 110th, how many photos you have at your house?
除了110小組那張 你還有多少照片
Not many. But she's framed, so she's important.
- 不多 - 但她的加了相框 所以她很重要
We're going to the Lucky Lounge.
我們要去幸運酒吧
No. You two stay here.
不 你們倆待在這里
You both look like cops.
你們倆看起來像警察
What do you two look like?
你們倆又像什么
Lady and the Tramp.
《小姐與流浪漢》
Hey. This woman working today?
嘿 這個女人今天上班嗎
Who are you?
你是誰
Friends of Jorge Sanchez.
豪爾赫桑切斯的朋友
Hey, Dulls.
嘿 杜爾斯
These guys say they're friends of Sanchez, want to talk to Milena.
這倆說他們是桑切斯的朋友 想跟米萊娜談談
Take them back to the office. She's doing the books.
帶他們去后面 她在記賬
Milena.
米萊娜
Take your shit and get out of here, now.
拿著你的東西 立刻離開這里
I get that he's a different kind of guy,
我知道他不一樣
but our commanding officer buys used underwear.
但我們的指揮官居然買二手內衣
Isn't that the girl from the photo? Oh, shit.
- 那不是照片里的女孩嗎  - 媽的
Hey!
嘿
This is as far as we're going.
我們就只能走到這里了
What's going on, fellas?
怎么回事 伙計們
You guys are gonna stop coming around here and messing with our friends.
別再來搞我們的朋友了
Look, pal, you somehow got...
聽我說 朋友 你有點...
Don't touch me!
別碰我
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
等等
Move your ass.
走啊
I'm done, I'm done.
別再打了 我受夠了
Well, it's a good thing O'Donnell and I didn't go in.
還好奧唐納和我沒進去
Something could've gone wrong.
否則可能會出岔子
You making friends, big fella?
你在交朋友嗎 大塊頭
I'm so sorry. I never would've run if I'd known who you were.
抱歉 如果我知道你們是誰 就不會逃跑了
I should've recognized you from Jorge's photos.
我應該認出你們的 我在豪爾赫的照片里看到過你們
My guys were just looking out for me.
我的朋友們只是想保護我
Scary dude came in here asking for her about a week ago.
大約一周前 一個可怕的家伙 來這里問過她
Said he was working with Sanchez and Orozco on some big security job.
那家伙說他和桑切斯以及奧羅斯科 一起在做某個大型安全工作
Broad-shouldered bald guy?
是個寬肩禿頂的家伙
No. He had hair.
不是 他有頭發
Scar down his cheek.
臉頰上有傷疤
He wanted to know if Sanchez had left any kind of digital storage device with me.
他想知道桑切斯有沒有 留給我任何數字存儲設備
I-I had no idea what he was talking about.
我不知道他在說什么
I got a bad vibe off the guy, so soon as he left, I called Jorge.
那家伙給我一種不祥的感覺 他一走 我就給豪爾赫打了電話
He didn't answer.
他沒接
They've gone dark before, part of the job, but this...
他們之前也因為工作失聯過 但這次
feels different.
感覺不一樣
Then you come in, claiming to know Sanchez,
你說你認識桑切斯
looking like the kind of people somebody'd hire to rough someone up.
而你看起來像是被雇來的打手
No offense. Assumed you were bad news.
無意冒犯 我以為你不可信
Do you know if Sanchez and Orozco had any recent contact
你知道桑切斯和奧羅斯科有沒有跟
with Calvin Franz or Tony Swan?
卡爾文弗朗茨或托尼斯旺聯系嗎
Actually, yeah. He was here a couple weeks ago. They hadn't seen each other in forever.
他幾周前來過 他們已經很久沒見面了
I took a picture of them.
我給他們拍了張照
They were working a case together.
他們當時在調查一起案子
Sanchez told you that? Yeah.
- 桑切斯跟你說的  - 是的
What was it?
什么案子
He didn't mention details.
他沒提細節
Was Swan involved?
斯旺也參與了嗎
He didn't come down to A.C.,
他沒來大西洋城
but I heard them mention his name.
但我聽到他們提到了他的名字
You tried asking Franz about this?
你們問過弗朗茨這件事嗎
- We can't. - Why not?
- 我們問不了 - 為什么
Someone threw him out of a helicopter.
有人把他從直升機上扔了下去
Oh, my God.
天啊
You think Jorge and Manuel are dead, too?
你們覺得豪爾赫 和曼努埃爾也死了嗎
We don't know yet.
我們還不知道
If they're alive, we'll find them, but we need your help.
如果他們還活著 我們會找到他們 但我們需要你幫忙
Is there anything else you can recall that you haven't told us?
你還記得什么沒告訴我們的事情嗎
I don't know.
我不知道
Last time I saw Jorge, he was sitting on that stool right there.
我上次看見豪爾赫時 他坐在那邊那張凳子上
He got a call. Seemed important.
他接了一個電話 似乎很重要
He say anything?
他說什么了
Kind of. He-he repeated a couple of numbers, kind of like he was surprised by them,
他重復了幾個數字 好像因此很驚訝
or-or worried, maybe.
或者擔心
Then he said he was going out for a while, and he never came back.
他說他要出去 然后就再也沒回來
Do you remember the numbers? Yeah.
- 你記得那些數字嗎  - 記得
He said,
他說
"650 at 100k each." No idea what he meant by that.
“六千五 每手十萬” 不知道是什么意思
You're sure that's what he said? I'm positive.
- 你確定  - 非常確定
He said, "650 at 100k,"
他說:“六千五 每手十萬”
he kissed me on the cheek and he ran out that door.
他吻了我的臉頰 跑出了那扇門
You remember the last words someone you love said to you.
你會記得你愛的人 對你說的最后一句話
We've got the numbers, we've got the New York plates.
我們已經掌握了數字 有紐約車牌
Maybe this isn't about someone with a grudge against the 110th.
也許這事與痛恨110小組的人無關
If you haven't noticed, it's pretty likely four of us have already been killed already.
我們中的四人很可能已經被殺害了
Milena said Franz was here a couple weeks ago.
米萊娜說弗朗茨幾周前來過這里
If the guys were onto something that made them think we were all in danger,
如果某些事讓他們覺得 我們處于危險之中
they would've called then, not weeks later.
那他們當時就會給我們打電話 而不是幾周后才打
650 at 100k, we're talking 65 million bucks.
六千五 每手十萬 我們說的是六千五百萬美元
That's a lot of black chips.
黑籌碼太多了
Most places. Not here.
大多數地方 不是這里
Atlantic City casinos rake in, what?
大西洋城的賭場大量斂財 怎么
Gross gaming revenue's got to be a couple billion a year, easy.
賭場的年總收入應該是幾十億
65 million, if taken carefully, over time,
六千五百萬 如果隨著時間的推移
could go unnoticed for a while.
可能會被忽視一段時間
Not that long. Not with casino accountants watching the take like hawks.
不會那么久 賭場會計會像老鷹一樣盯著
But could the bad guys hide it in the margins long enough to get away with it
有沒有可能是壞人將其藏得夠久
before the calculator crew catches on?
在會計發現之前逃脫懲罰
Sanchez and Orozco do freelance casino security.
桑切斯和奧羅斯科 是自由職業賭場保安
I mean, maybe it all started with them.
也許事情是從他們開始的
They stumbled onto something big, they needed help...
他們偶然發現了一件大事 需要幫忙
So they reached out to Franz... maybe Swan.
所以他們聯系了弗朗茨 或許還有斯旺
Guess this whole thing could be tied to gaming.
這件事可能與賭博有關
I'm Ellie, I'll be your server. What can I get you?
我是艾莉 為你們服務 你們需要什么
The casino's director of security.
我們找安全總監
Now, please.
請立刻帶我們去吧
So, you're the 110th.
你們是110小組的
What's left of us.
是我們組剩下的成員
Sanchez and Orozco talk about you guys all the time.
桑切斯和奧羅斯科總是提起你們
Please.
請坐
So, you knew them well?
你之前很了解他們嗎
Uh, yeah. They would do background checks for all the casinos on the boardwalk.
是的 他們會對木板人行道 所有賭場進行背景調查
Hold on. Uh, you just said "knew them."
等等 你剛說:“之前了解”
Past tense.
過去時
We have reason to believe they might be dead.
我們認為他們可能已經死了
Oh, shit.
見鬼
I-I just saw them, uh, while I was picking up lunch at White House Subs last month.
我上個月在白宮三明治店 吃午餐的時候還見過他們
How can I help? These numbers mean anything to you?
- 我能幫什么忙嗎  - 這些數據有什么意義嗎
Not offhand.
就這么看沒什么意義
What about the phrase, "650 at 100k each"?
那“六千五 每手十萬”呢
No. Uh, what's this all about?
不知道 這究竟是怎么回事
We think Sanchez and Orozco
桑切斯和奧羅斯科可能一直在調查
may have been looking into a $65 million gambling scam.
一起價值六千五百萬的賭博騙局
Okay.
好吧
Uh, well, in that case, your "650" could be rigged slot machines or fixed hands of poker,
你們說的“六千五”可能是 被操縱的老虎機或固定手牌
but at 100k per hand, that'd be incredibly high stakes.
但每手十萬 那可是相當高的賭注
And I can tell you right now, our books are on mark.
我現在就可以告訴你們 我們的賬都是對的
All right? We're not missing a penny.
一分錢都不少
What about your competitors?
那你的競爭對手呢
You know, I can... I can ask around,
我可以打聽一下
see if anyone knew what Sanchez and Orozco were working on.
看是否有人知道桑切斯 和奧羅斯科在調查什么案子
That might narrow it down for you. While you're at it, run these names,
- 那樣可能會縮小范圍 - 你打聽時 也順道查查這些名字
see if any of them are registered at a hotel in town.
看是否有人用其中的名字 登記入住酒店
Uh... you know, this-this might take a few hours. Where are you guys staying?
這可能要花幾個小時 你們住哪兒
Don't know yet.
我們還不知道
Well, then, please, allow me.
那請讓我來安排吧
Not necessary.
不需要
No, no. Any friends of Sanchez and Orozco.
那不行 你們可是 桑切斯和奧羅斯科的朋友
Well, it looks like all we have available is a suite.
看來我們現在只有一間套房了
I guess that'll have to do.
我猜那也夠了吧
Come on, I'll get you guys settled in.
跟我來 我會安排你們安頓下來
We'll be fine at a motel. Reacher,
- 我們去住汽車旅館就行了 - 雷徹
when someone offers to comp you a suite, just say yes.
當有人請你免費住套房時 直接答應就好
Yeah. We'll have them send you up a park bench to sleep on.
我們會讓他們送你 一張公園長椅 讓你睡覺
You'll feel right at home.
你會有賓至如歸的感覺
What was that about a motel, Reacher?
雷徹 你不會還想住汽車旅館吧
Whoa. I bet this place has a spa.
這地方肯定有水療中心
I'm gonna take a schvitz.
我要蒸桑拿
Ooh. Dibs on the ocean view.
這還是個海景房
O'Donnell and Neagley found the bar.
奧唐納和內格利找到了吧臺
It's fully stocked.
里面“庫存”充足
Not for long. You unpacked?
不過一會就不夠了 放好行李了嗎
Yup.
好了
I haven't been in a hotel that wasn't advertised as "family friendly" in years.
我很多年沒住過 沒標榜“家庭友好”的酒店了
I still can't believe David O'Donnell procreated.
我還是不敢相信 大衛奧唐納有孩子了
On purpose, anyway.
還是計劃生育
Yeah, I seem to remember someone bragging that the only people that would call you Daddy
我記得某人曾吹噓說 唯一稱你為“爸爸”的人
were the women you slept with.
是跟你睡過的女人
I still sleep with people who call me Daddy.
我現在還跟叫我“爸爸”的人一起睡
Sometimes all three of them if it's thundering outside.
如果外面打雷 我還是跟三個一起睡
You'll find out soon enough, Dixon.
你很快就會知道的 迪克森
You're pregnant? What?
- 你懷孕了  - 什么
No. Shit no.
沒有
No, she's engaged. What, you didn't know?
她訂婚了 怎么 你不知道
Someone finally lassoed our little filly.
終于有人套住了我們的小母馬
No,
不
I, um, didn't...
我不知道
Yeah. Well, about that, you guys can, uh, unsave the date.
關于訂婚那事 你們不必留時間過來了
Fuck. Seriously?
好家伙 真的
Yeah, I mean, you know me. I've always been a numbers gal, always had a life plan.
你了解我的 我一直是個數字女孩 一直都有人生計劃
Plan said to get married at a certain age, certain year.
計劃在一定的年齡 某一年結婚
And then one day, I see text messages on his phone.
然后 一天 我看到了他手機上的短信
It says, "Hey, sweetheart, can't wait to see you Friday.
說:“嘿 親愛的 等不及周五見面了
I miss you." And all of that.
-“我愛你”等等 - 不是吧
No. No one steps out on Dixon.
沒人能對迪克森不忠
Not even him, apparently.
顯然他也不行
Text messages were from his niece who was visiting.
短信是他即將來拜訪的侄女發的
But I realized that when I thought he was cheating,
但我發現當我以為他出軌時
I was, uh...
我...
I was relieved.
我松了一口氣
I mean, he's a decent man. I...
他是個很正直的人 我...
I don't know, if you're gonna spend the rest of your life with somebody,
如果你要和某人共度一生
don't you want to feel something more than comfort?
難道你不想感受一些 舒服之外的東西嗎
I mean, don't you want to feel excitement,
難道你不想覺得刺激
a little jolt of something when you see him?
當你看見他時 有一點震動的感覺嗎
Anyways, you know, for a moment I thought I was gonna get out of it with no mess and no guilt,
有那么一刻 我以為 我會平靜且毫無內疚地擺脫婚姻
but instead, I got out of it with...
但相反 我擺脫了婚姻...
A lot of mess and a whole lot of guilt.
卻非常混亂 滿滿的負罪感
Bingo.
答對了
Good for you.
這對你來說是好事
Karla Dixon doesn't settle.
卡拉迪克森沒有安定下來
Thank you.
謝謝
That's actually why I took the undercover job.
因此我接了臥底工作
Take a little time away from it all.
花一點時間遠離這一切
Explain to me how undercover work and forensic accounting go together?
給我解釋一下 你怎么會同時當臥底和法務會計的
Well, um, CEO embezzling millions from a company down in Texas,
首席執行官從德州一家公司 侵吞了數百萬美元
where everybody's packing some kind of heat, and he was the kind of guy to use it if cornered,
那里每個人都攜帶槍支 如果被逼到絕路 他絕對會用武器
so got a little intrigue along with the number-crunching.
所以除了數字分析之外 還有一點吸引力
All right.
好吧
And what about you, Neagley?
你呢 內格利
Every time I check my LinkedIn, you're getting promoted again.
我每次查看領英網 都看到你升職了
I'm having fun.
我過得很好
On big cases, running a team now.
解決了大案子 現在帶團隊
Trying to land this huge software company as a client.
我之前試著 跟一家龐大的軟件公司簽合同
I pull it off, I get a taste of that fat contract.
我成功了 從那份值錢的合同里面收獲頗豐
Making it rain.
賺了不少錢啊
No choice. I really want to get my dad on round-the-clock nursing care
我別無選擇 我想給我爸請全天候護理
and rent him a nice place closer to me, but that takes capital.
給他租個離我近的房子 但那需要錢
Why rent? Buy and build equity.
為什么要租呢 直接買下來
Get a condo. Co-ops are fucking banana republics.
不 搞套公寓 合作社就是他媽的香蕉共和國
Yeah.
是啊
What about you, big dog? Being awfully quiet over there.
你呢 大狗狗 幾乎音信全無
Home ownership is like keeping snakes as pets or ballroom dancing competitions.
置業就像養蛇當寵物 或參加交際舞比賽
Fine, if that's what you're into.
如果你對此感興趣 那沒問題
I just don't see the appeal. Or the appeal of a steady job.
- 但我不喜歡 - 那你覺得穩定的工作有吸引力嗎
Corporate world doesn't seem that different from the Army,
企業界似乎跟軍隊也沒什么區別
and that always felt a little like a cage.
總感覺像是個牢籠
Just didn't know anything else.
只是不知道其他的事情
Then one day I was in a bar, and someone plays Howlin' Wolf
我之前在酒吧里 有人演奏《狼嚎》
singing about trains going by in the night.
歌唱夜晚路過的火車
That sounded like real freedom to me.
那聽起來像是真正的自由
Are you jumping on freight trains like Boxcar Willie?
你像博科思卡爾威利一樣 跳上貨運列車
Sometimes.
有時
Mostly I take buses or hitchhike.
大多數時候 我坐公交車或搭便車
What kind of lunatic is picking up the world's biggest drifter?
哪種瘋子才會讓世界上 塊頭最大的流浪漢上車啊
They can be interesting. Where do you eat?
- 他們很有意思 - 你在哪里吃飯
I steal pie off windowsills.
我從窗臺上偷餡餅
I'm being serious. Diners.
- 我說真的 - 小飯館
Sometimes people who pick me up share a meal with me.
有時讓我搭便車的人 會分享食物 跟我一起吃飯
Sometimes I share with them. Where do you sleep?
- 有時是我分享給他們 - 你睡哪兒
Cheap motels mostly.
大多數時候住在廉價汽車旅館里
And what if you can't find one?
如果你找不到汽車旅館呢
Unattended boats in marinas are good for a night.
停泊在碼頭的無人看管的船只 也很適合住一晚
Flatbeds of parked trucks.
熄火的卡車的平板也適合
Had a great night's sleep in a hammock I spotted in some guy's backyard once
有一次 我在發現的吊床上 睡了個好覺
till the sprinklers went off. Good God, man.
- 可惜灑水器澆滅了我的美夢 - 天啊
All you need is a stick and a bindle. Too much luggage.
- 你還真是一根棍和一塊布就走天下 - 行李太多了
Any more questions?
還有問題嗎
Yeah, just one.
有 只有一個
Don't you ever get lonely?
你從來不覺得孤單嗎
Looks like someone took the sign as a personal challenge.
有人把標語當成個人挑戰了呀
Doreen, I'm just warming up.
多琳 我只是在熱身
If you liked the dinner, make sure to try Neptune's breakfast buffet.
如果你喜歡晚餐 請務必試一下尼普頓的自助早餐
Every day, starting at 6:00 a.m.
每天早上六點開始
Thank you.
謝謝
Looks like I'm not the only one who couldn't sleep.
看來我不是唯一一個睡不著的
Numbers relax me.
數字讓我放松
Figured if I was gonna do math, I might as well make some walking-around money. Stand.
如果我要做點數學計算 不如順便賺點錢 我要叫停
Ma'am, you're showing ten and eight on two of your hands.
你的兩只手上顯示的是十和八
That's right. And I could double down and risk it all for a potentially larger payout.
沒錯 我可以加倍下注 賭上一切換取更大的回報
Or I could stand and have a guaranteed win
或者我也可以叫停 保證能獲勝
because the next card out of that shoe is gonna bust you.
因為下一張牌亮牌時 你就輸光了
My grandmother always said, pigs get fat, hogs get slaughtered.
我祖母曾經說 “不可人心不足蛇吞象”
She's no hog.
她可不是蛇
I'm no hog, so I'm gonna stand.
我不是蛇 所以我要叫停
As you wish.
如你所愿
15...
十五
Too many.
太多了
Congratulations, ma'am.
恭喜你 女士
You're having a very lucky night.
你今晚非常幸運
Maybe you'd like to celebrate with a concert on us?
我們想請你去聽音樂會 慶祝一下
Thank you. Ladies of the '80s.
- 謝謝 - 八十年代的女士們
Debbie Gibson, Tiffany, and Taylor Dane performing their biggest hits.
黛比吉布森 蒂芙尼和泰勒戴恩 會表演她們最熱門的歌曲
If you hurry, you can actually catch the second half.
你可以趕上下半場
But I'm having fun.
但我玩得很開心
Ma'am, we know you're counting cards.
我們知道你在算牌
Which isn't illegal if you do it in your head.
用腦子算牌是合法的
But seeing that your chief of security was kind enough to comp us a suite,
但鑒于你們的安全主管 好心給我們安排了一間套房
I'll cut you some slack.
我就放你們一馬吧
Want to use those muscles and help me carry these to the cashier window?
動動你的肌肉 把這些籌碼送到收銀窗口去
And you can give these tickets to the guy in the Members Only jacket.
把這些票給穿著會員專用夾克的人
He looks like he would enjoy some '80s ladies.
他看起來很喜歡八十年代的女士
Thanks for coming with.
謝謝你陪我
Late-night walks always clear my head,
深夜散步總能讓我頭腦清醒
and after the text I got from Neagley about Franz, my head's been kind of cloudy, you know?
我收到內格利發來說弗朗茨死了的 短信后 我的腦子就一直有點亂
Yeah.
是啊
I'm surprised you can walk at all with all the casino's money in your pockets.
我很驚訝你口袋里 裝著賭場賺來的那些錢還能散步
Can I assume the forensic accountant's gonna declare that cash on her taxes?
我猜法務會計會在稅款申報的時候 附上這一筆錢吧
Those crooks?
那些騙子
If there's anybody I could audit... Actually, it's kind of my dream job.
要是我能審計某人的話 那簡直是我夢想的工作
Current gig doesn't give you your auditing fix?
現在的工作滿足不了你嗎
No, I'm just busting millionaires from stealing from billionaires.
不行 我正在抓一個 從億萬富翁那里偷錢的百萬富翁
What I really want to do is go after government corruption and waste.
我想做的是追查 政府的腐敗和浪費行為
Oh, you used to work for Uncle Sam.
你以前在山姆大叔手下工作過
You know what I'm talking about. $600 toilet seats. Exactly.
- 六百美元的坐便圈 - 沒錯
I mean, if tax money was spent efficiently, honestly, we could fix roads and bridges
如果稅收能被有效使用 我們可以修路和橋梁
and schools. Like, we could help people who actually need help.
以及學校 我們可以幫助需要幫助的人
We could make a difference.
我們可以有所作為
You should do it.
你應該這么做
Yeah.
是啊
Well, I looked into starting my own nonprofit watchdog group,
我考慮過自己成立非營利監督組織
but start-up costs are prohibitive.
但啟動成本讓人望而卻步
First step's always the hardest.
第一步總是最難的
Yeah.
是的
Is that why, back in the day, you and I never happened?
這就是我們以前 從沒有發生過關系的原因嗎
First steps were the hardest?
第一步是最難的
How much did you drink back at the hotel room?
你在酒店房間里喝了多少
Enough to ask you that question.
足夠我問你那個問題了
I mean, come on, Reacher. It's not like I didn't drop any hints.
快說 我以前給過你提示
I was your boss.
當時我是你的老大
It wouldn't have been right.
那樣做不對
Wow. [sighs] Well, I waited years for that answer, and it's pure Reacher.
我等了好幾年才等到這個答案 不愧是你雷徹的作風
Direct, honest and well-reasoned.
直接 誠實且有理有據
So, can I ask you another question?
我能再問你個問題嗎
What do you want to do about the two guys that are following us?
你想怎么對付那兩個跟蹤我們的人
When'd you spot them? Ooh, when we left the casino.
- 你什么時候發現的  - 我們離開賭場時就發現了
Figure they saw us cashing out and now they're gonna try to rob us.
我以為他們是看到我們兌的現金 想搶劫我們
That's what I thought, too.
我本來也是這么想的
But see that car
看見停在那邊
parked up the street with the New York dealer tags? Yeah.
- 有紐約臨時牌照的車了嗎  - 怎么了
Pretty sure it was behind us on the expressway when we came into town.
我們進城時 它在高速路上跟著我們
Also, pretty sure when we walk by it, a man with a gun will step out.
我們經過它時 肯定會有個持槍的男人走出來
Then, when we turn to run, the guys behind us won't be so far behind anymore.
我們轉身逃跑時 我們身后的人 不會離得那么遠
So what's the plan?
計劃是什么
We're not gonna walk by that car.
我們不會經過那輛車
On my "go," over the fence.
我說“走” 就翻過柵欄
Go.
走
Fuck.
他媽的
Okay, there's got to be a warrant out for you in New York for hitting that cop.
好的 因為你打了那個警察 肯定會發布你的逮捕令
We open fire in a residential area, cops get called, you get locked up.
如果我們在住宅區開槍 警察就會被叫來 你會被關起來
Let's do this without guns.
我們別用槍
Looks like they have the same idea.
看起來他們也是這么想的
Need help with yours?
需要我幫你處理你負責的人嗎
I'll manage.
我能處理
Damn, Reacher. When we were kids, we just wrote our names in it.
該死 我們小時候 會把名字寫在混凝土里
It's the Members Only jacket guy from the casino.
是賭場里穿著會員專用夾克的男人
Oh, shit. If they went after us, they might go after Neagley and O'Donnell, too.
媽的 如果他們追殺我們 他們可能也會去追殺內格利和奧唐納
No, they waited until we were off the boardwalk to make their move.
不會 他們一直等到我們離開 木板人行道才動手
They're not gonna go into a busy hotel with cameras everywhere.
他們不會去 到處都是監控的繁忙的酒店
No I.D.
沒有身份證
Let's search this asshole's car.
我們搜一下這個混蛋的車
Looks like someone did their homework.
看起來有人做了功課
Phone.
手機
Is it done?
成了嗎
Not in the way you expected.
成是成了 就是跟你想的不一樣
You're fucking with the wrong guy, Reacher.
你惹錯人了
You should know that this doesn't end well for you.
你應該知道你不會有好下場的
Then why are you the one that sounds scared?
那為什么是你聽起來在瑟瑟發抖
Think I got his attention. Should we trace the number?
- 我覺得我引起他的注意了 - 我們要追蹤號碼嗎
This is a burner. Guy on the other end will be using a burner, too.
這是一次性手機 剛才接電話那人也會用一次性手機
Dealer tags are most likely ghost plates, VIN's been scratched off.
臨時牌照是幽靈車牌 車牌號已經被刮掉了
Nothing to I.D. any of them.
沒什么能指認他們身份的東西
These guys are pros.
這些人都是專業殺手
We should've left one of them alive.
我們應該留個活口的
Yeah, but they didn't give us much of a choice, did they?
是啊 他們沒給我們很多選擇
Maybe not. Now we have nothing to go on.
也許沒有 現在我們的線索斷了
Not necessarily.
不一定
Parking lot pass.
停車場通行證
"New Age Technologies." Yeah.
-“新時代科技” - 對
Stamped yesterday morning.
昨天早上蓋的章
I think it's what you call a clue.
這就是你口中的線索
Now what are we gonna do about those bodies?
我們怎么處理尸體
I have an idea.
我有個主意
I'm thirsty.
我口渴了
Want to get a beer?
想喝啤酒嗎
Anything on New Age?
新時代有什么發現嗎
Yeah,
有
looks like New Age is an aerospace company.
看起來新時代是一家航空航天公司
Any ties to Atlantic City?
跟大西洋城有聯系嗎
Not that I can see. Headquarters are based in New York.
我看沒有 它的總部設在紐約
Looks like a piece of shrapnel bit me. I didn't notice with all the adrenaline pumping.
有一塊彈片打中我了 剛才太過刺激 我沒注意
Barely winged you.
幾乎沒傷到你
Here.
這里...
What you doing?
你在干什么
What my mom used to do when the alcohol stung.
給傷口抹酒精很疼 我媽以前就這么做
You know, you're probably just blowing germs into it.
你可能只把細菌吹進去了
Probably. But it feels good.
可能吧 但感覺很好
Thanks.
謝謝
Welcome.
不用謝
You know, Reacher,
你知道 雷徹
it's perfectly normal to be lonely sometimes.
有時感覺孤單是很正常的
Anyone living their life the way you do would.
任何人像你這么過日子都會孤單
But you don't have to be lonely tonight.
今晚你不必孤單
And you're not my boss anymore.
而且你也不再是我的老大了
All 650 will be in the truck.
所有六千五百萬都將裝在卡車里
You can track the shipment with the GPS locater I paired to this.
你可以用我在車上 裝的GPS定位器追蹤
There are at least two good ambush points marked on the route.
路上至少標記了兩個好的伏擊點
Excellent.
很好
My men will take care of the rest.
我的人會處理剩下的事
And the weapons?
那武器呢
They'll all be used overseas? I was told that was the deal.
都會在海外使用嗎 這是說好了的
Absolutely.
那當然
And the, and the truck driver won't be harmed?
卡車司機不會受到傷害吧
Of course.
當然
I would never harm anyone.
我永遠不會傷害任何人
Morning, Dixon. We need to talk to you about what happened last night.
- 早上好 迪克森 - 我們需要談談昨晚的事
Oh, the whole hotel heard what happened last night.
整個酒店都聽到昨天的動靜了
Told you you were loud.
我就說你聲音很大
Found this in a car that followed us down from New York yesterday.
這是昨天在從紐約就開始 跟蹤我們的車里找到的
What happened to the driver?
司機怎么了
He won't be following us back.
他不會跟我們回去
Neither will his two friends.
他的那兩個朋友也不會
Shit.
媽的
Who is it? Wright.
- 是誰  - 賴特
Clear.
安全
Come on in.
進來
You, uh, you folks seem a little jumpy.
你們看起來有點緊張啊
I mean, I don't blame you, given the circumstances.
鑒于目前的情況 我不能怪你們
And I hate to be the bearer of more bad news, but when I was looking into things,
我很討厭傳達更多壞消息 但我調查這些事情時
Atlantic City PD told me that two more bodies have been discovered in Upstate New York,
大西洋城警察局跟我說 他們在紐約北部發現了兩具尸體
near where they found your other friend.
就在他們發現你們朋友的地方附近
Judging by the decomposition, they'd been there a while.
從分解情況來看 他們已經在那兒有段時間了
Got a copy of the police report for you.
我拿到了一份警察報告副本
Pretty easy to I.D. him with that.
很容易借此識別其身份
When he joined the Army, his sister was terrified
他參軍時 他姐姐很害怕
he'd be killed with some disfiguring wounds.
他會傷痕累累地死去
She'd never know what happened to him.
她永遠不會知道發生了什么
Said his dog tags could be blown off.
就說他的兵牌可能被炸掉
To calm her down, he got his name and service number tattooed across his back.
為了安撫她 他在后背上 文了他的名字和服役編號
Looked ridiculous.
看起來很可笑
He didn't care.
他不在乎
He loved his sister.
他愛他的姐姐
I'm gonna have to call her.
我得給她打電話
I'll tell Milena about Jorge.
我會告訴米萊娜豪爾赫的遭遇
Their wounds match Franzy's.
他們的傷口跟弗朗茨的吻合
Meaning he was tortured and tossed out of a helicopter.
這意味著他受到了折磨 然后被扔下了直升機
Uh, one other thing.
還有一件事
Um, no one using any of the names you gave me have checked into any of the hotels in town.
沒有人用你給我的名字 登記入住任何酒店
And I talked to my counterparts at the other casinos.
我跟其他賭場的同行談過了
Orozco and Sanchez, they weren't working on anything for any of them.
奧羅斯科和桑切斯 沒有替他們查任何案子
And when I told them about the $65 million gambling scam,
我跟他們說六千五百萬的賭博騙局時
they pulled their overnight audits. I did, too.
他們連夜查賬 我也是
Everything is within acceptable loss margins.
一切都在可接受的損失幅度中
No one has hit any of the casinos.
沒有人以任何一家賭場為目標
You don't have anything to worry about.
你不必擔心
Bodies were found in New York, car that followed us was from New York.
尸體都是在紐約發現的 跟蹤我們的車是從紐約來的
New York ghost tags, New York parking pass.
是紐約的幽靈車牌和停車證件
This has always been a New York case.
這一直是紐約的案子
Where the hell are you going?
你要去哪里
We're gonna need more guns.
我們需要更多的槍